But I don't want to give up.
In the cracks in the bottom of the world.
I have been born in the world.
I will surely find this way.
I will change the world.
I will change the world?
Thank you.
Fighting God!
recent directive now.
Here it is.
After the initial greeting, it
says he input the information
onto this disk when we
boarded the train in Napoli.
It goes on, saying,
I therefore have no means of knowing the
number of your pursuers
at the present moment,
nor do I know the number
of men you have possibly lost
in your battles until now.
This disk will tell you the best
way for us to safely
rendezvous with my daughter.
It will be your final mission.
Also know this,
it is absolutely imperative that you
follow my instructions to the letter.
This condition
is non-negotiable.
If you or your men deviate from my
directive, regardless of whether the
act is accidental, I'll be forced to
consider it an overt act of betrayal.
And now for my directive.
You are to travel to the
island of San Giorgiorno Major.
There, with my daughter in tow, you
shall go to the top of the bell tower.
Upon your safe delivery of my child,
you will have completed the mission.
Rule number one.
There is no stairway to the top,
and only one elevator can reach
the peak of the bell tower.
Only Trish and one protector shall
be allowed to board that elevator.
Rule 2.
Said protector must have no knives, guns,
or cell phones, or any
other objects on them.
Rule 3.
From the moment you retrieve this disc,
you will have 15 minutes to disembark.
This disc is outfitted with a transmitter,
which will allow me to
follow your movements.
Rule 4.
The others must remain on the boat
and are forbidden from coming ashore.
That is all.
We've made it.
Time to do this.
So the boss is at the
top of that tower, huh?
Well, he's certainly detailed
and extremely careful.
But given that he's the head of the
entire organization, makes sense.
It's strange knowing that this
will be the end of our mission.
But we're alive.
Couldn't ask for more than that.
Yeah, we're alive all
right, but just barely.
We made it to the City of Water.
We should have some fun.
This place has great cuisine.
They've got good chow here, too?
I didn't realize how hungry I
was, but my tummy's rumbling.
So what are the local specialties?
They've got squid ink pasta
and horsehair crab salad,
not to mention the carpaccio that's
served at the Hotel Cipriani.
It's to die for.
Have you lost it?
In case you've forgotten,
we are still on assignment!
Narancia, keep an eye
on the radar. Uh, sure.
Bucciaratti, I would like to offer
myself up to be Trisha's guardian.
Let me do this.
Let me go with her to the bell tower.
Just who the hell do
you think you are, kid?
Uchirati's our Cape, so he's taking
her to the boss, arrogant prick.
The boss would have designated someone to
do it himself if he knew
who was still alive.
Thank you, but I must go.
Let's move, Trish.
Two were requested, and two it shall be.
This is it.
Our chance to learn the boss's identity.
I won't let it slip by.
Listen, Giorno.
Given that this is our last mission,
mind lending me a little bit of luck?
Some see them as children of the
sun, others as symbols of life.
It's like a talisman, yes?
Well, I guess so. Yes.
Ladybugs are bringers of good luck.
This brooch is pulsating with
life thanks to Golden Wind.
It will serve as our beacon.
Bucciarati.
Yes, Fugo?
This seems the most
fitting time to tell you.
Why so formal?
Thing is, I always knew that you
were destined to become Cape.
I also know you'll see this
mission through to the very end.
Well, of course he will.
Together, I know we'll rise
all the way to the top.
Yes, that we will.
The time's come. Let's go.
As long as I can find a way
to affix this to the boss,
Giorno will be able to
track his every move.
We will unveil the boss's identity.
We have to.
He left the door open.
Our options are the
ground floor or the tower.
Straight shot and nowhere to stop.
What is...
what is going to happen to me?
First, I'm kidnapped
by a bunch of mafiosi.
My life is threatened.
Then, to top it off, now I'm being
dragged off to a father I've never met.
So, where am I supposed to go from here?
No need to worry.
Your safety is the boss's concern.
As for your path moving forward, I
believe I can offer some insight.
You'll be given a different name, after
which you may need to alter your appearance.
And you'll likely assume a new identity.
You'll reside somewhere far away from us,
but at long last, you'll
truly know happiness.
I assure you, Trish, your
father can make that happen.
Here, take my hand.
No.
I'm not afraid.
Not in the slightest.
I wonder if I'll one day
grow to love my father.
Those aren't the kinds of
things families worry about.
You're right.
What was I thinking?
It's strange to worry my
head over things like that.
We're here.
This is it.
Trish! Trish!
What the hell?
Her hand? But how?
When did...
We're supposed to be the only
ones currently in this place.
The only people who even
know about this are my
team and there's no way
could the boss have really
Was this to protect his identity this
mission all the agony we've been through
what the hell Was it for did he only lure
us all here to kill her with his own hands
Bruno Bucciarati was born the son of a
fisherman in a small town outside Napoli.
Often labeled as standoffish, Bruno's
father lived a life of integrity.
More than anything, he fought to protect
his family from life's cruelties.
I'm back, Bruno. Papa!
The net needs mending.
I've got it.
Bruno's mother had a kind heart, and their
frequent chats always warmed his soul.
He especially looked forward
to her nightly bedtime stories.
Okay, time for bed.
However, everything changed when
Bucciarati was seven. What now?
What do you do?
I don't know, but this can't go on.
I need to leave and find my way.
After ten years of marriage,
his parents divorced.
No one except his parents would ever know
the reason why their relationship ended.
And Bruno?
Where'll he stay?
The one thing his parents
agreed on was that the
decision of where he would
live was Bruno's to make.
Bruno, I want you to know Mama and
Papa love you more than anything.
But we think it's best we live apart.
I'm sorry, my baby.
That's how it has to be.
But we wanted to give you a choice.
Do you want to come with me?
Or would you rather stay
and live here with Papa?
You've always been such a bright boy.
You could get a good education.
Oh, and there'll be other
kids your age to play with.
You want to come and
live with Mama, right?
I know you do.
Actually, I think I'll
stay here with Papa. Huh?
You don't mean that.
Bruno, don't make a rash decision.
You've always liked Mama best.
I'm staying here and keeping Papa company.
You can't!
Mama will be alright no
matter where she goes.
But Papa...
This is goodbye.
I promise you, honey,
I'll visit every month.
Yeah.
Bucciarati's instincts proved correct.
Two years after his mother's departure,
she remarried a Milanese man.
After that, he would only
see his mother at Christmas.
All that had a curious
effect on her former husband,
who became possessed with the idea
of sending his son to a good school.
Papa, shouldn't the
customers be arriving soon?
Oh, yeah.
I lost track of time.
I'll go ahead and recast the nets then.
Okay.
This one's all yours.
Bruno's father had always
worked as a fisherman,
but now that he was putting
his son through school,
he needed to use his boat to make money
with tourists and visiting fishermen.
And so, the Wheel of
Destiny steadily turned.
I'm sorry, signore.
That island isn't ideal for fishing.
The other one...
I don't give a damn.
We want to go fishing
there, so we're going to go.
Just shut up and do your
freaking job, boat man.
Got it?
Yeah, right away.
Later that evening,
the Coast Guard would
find Bucciarati's father,
his body devastated with bullet wounds.
GSWs to the arms, shoulders,
chest, and abdomen.
Seven total.
The bullets are still in him.
Papa!
Please wait until the surgery is over.
Just try and calm down.
Are there any family members we can call?
Papa.
This is evidence.
Make sure forensics gets it.
Si, signore. I'm off. Right.
How could this have happened?
Good evening.
Are you his son?
We found this at the crime scene.
It seems your father became an
accidental witness to a drug deal.
He was shot to ensure his silence.
Your father's a very important
witness to this case,
so trust me when I say we're all
rooting for him to pull through.
Drugs?
Drugs put my papa in here?
Miraculously, Bucciarati's
father survived the surgery.
The seven bullets that tore through
his flesh missed critical organs.
Those who found him were equipped
with the necessary life-saving tools,
buying him time to get to the hospital.
It was a true miracle.
But as far as Bucciarati's
life was concerned,
it may have been better if his
father hadn't survived at all.
Sometimes, life makes it impossible
to make the right choice.
Life gets messy.
Lines get blurred.
Damn fisherman.
You just don't know when
to call it quits, do ya?
I'll keep watch, just hurry up and do it!
You're a pain for making
us make a night call.
Do us all a favor and die!
Who the hell are you?
You kidding me?
It's just some punk kid!
What the hell are you doing?
He's just a kid!
Smash the damn knife away!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I won't let them hurt you, Papa.
Leave it all to me.
You just worry about getting better.
At age 12,
Bruno Bucciarati had become a murderer,
and a murderer he would
remain the rest of his life.
I can't turn back now.
Not when they want to
permanently shut us up.
And I can't count on the police.
The only organization that could
protect them ruled from the shadows.
The Family.
Ujarati knocked on its doors.
And in exchange for his service and
loyalty, protection was finally guaranteed.
He saw it as the embodiment of
justice and gave his all for it.
He soon made a name for himself
and caught the eye of Cape Polpo.
Five years later, Bucciarati's father
died from complications from his wounds.
Bucciarati despised the white
powder of greed that had brought
them into this hell and swore
to battle it with all his might.
However...
I'm sorry!
I promise I'll leave him alone!
I'll never bother him again!
That'd be wise.
Regret is an emotion
felt only by the living.
But if you're a mafioso...
What in the hell?
Hey!
What's in the bags?
Buterati realized that the
boss, his model of justice,
profited from the drugs he so despised.
This filth's being peddled in my city?
It was supposed to be prohibited!
Now the boss is our damn boss.
His wretchedness makes me want to puke.
Abusing the weak and innocent
is just a means to an end.
Profiting from the pain and
suffering of countless citizens?
Coward.
You do it to your daughter.
You're a fiendish monster.
You're a disgrace and you've
You let me down again,
but you've done it for the last time!
There, Trisha's still alive.
Good, it's stuck.
God's hope, I didn't see his face.
At first, I was content with uncovering
your identity, but everything's changed.
After what you've done, die!
Think fast.
The boss still assumes that
I'm absolutely loyal to him.
He'll die by assassination.
I'll ambush him as he tries to
escape and kill the bastard.
Wait, this is...
this opening.
Of course, the demented bastard
would hide in the crypt of a church.
He thinks he can murder
Trish in complete anonymity.
His plan must be to pass through the crypt
to escape the building on the other side.
But I'm lying in wait.
There!
In position now leave
while you're still able
Bucciarati step out from behind that
pillar and lose your life in the process
Go! Zippermen!
He'll rip it off!
Somehow, he figured out I was here.
But now, he's resorted to
hiding in the shadows again.
I need to find his
weakness, whatever it is.
Your rationale intrigues me.
Just what were you thinking?
I had a great deal of respect for your
excellence and devotion
to the mission until now.
Was your judgment clouded
by your promotion to Cape?
Or did your hubris
seduce you into thinking
you had the power and
ability to overtake me?
Once Trish regains consciousness, I'll be
sure to let her know you never existed.
Trish, you say?
Why bring her into this dispute?
My daughter is of no concern
to you and your ilk demon.
You could never understand
what's in my heart.
Hey, Giorno.
We're on it, Bucciarati.
Tracking down his movements as we speak.
The brooch will tell me exactly
where he is at all times.
Right now, he's at the bottom
of the stairs to the crypt.
He's next to the pillar, about
two meters away from the stairs.
But wait, Bucerati! Something's wrong!
Until we know what it is, don't attack!
End him!
Zipperman!
It wasn't him hiding
in the pillar's shadow.
It was me!
What...
what the...
What is going on?
Think of this as a gift, a
farewell gift from the heart.
In a moment, you will cease to exist,
so I will allow you to know now.
What you witnessed and felt
was your future self laid bare.
Simply put, your past
self saw a future version.
Now behold, know the almighty
power of Emperor Crimson.
I obliterated time, then leapt beyond it.
It doesn't matter who it is.
I shall never allow any Cretan to
threaten my eternal transcendence.
Not ever.
The time's come for you to fade away.
Mucharate, your mission as
protector has been terminated.
Now may the fires of hell embrace you.
Thank you.